Terror is on the line.
Final Caller is a horror, comedy film directed by Todd Sheets.
Roland Bennett, an obnoxious late-night presenter specializing
in the supernatural is not having a good night!
A visit from his soon-to-be ex-wife brings divorce papers to the station, a boss listening in due to
complaints, and finally, a call from The Outsider threatening to kill a woman live on the phone.
Is it a prank?
Roland Bennett, played by Douglas Epps.
Jessica, played by Rachel Lagen.
Jason, played by Alexander Brotherton.
The Outsider, played by Jack McCord.
Claire, played by Jane Plumberg.
The Detective, played by Antwoine Steele.
Phone Booth is a 2002 American psychological thriller film directed by Joel Schumacher, produced by David Zucker and Gil Netter,
written by Larry Cohen and starring Colin Farrell, Forest Whitaker, Katie Holmes, Radha Mitchell, and Kiefer Sutherland.
In the film, a malevolent hidden sniper calls a phone booth, and when a young
publicist inside answers the phone, he quickly finds his life is at risk.
Produced by Fox 2000 Pictures and Zucker/Netter Productions, the film premiered at the 2002 Toronto
International Film Festival, and was set to be theatrically released in November 2002, but the D.C.
sniper attacks in October 2002 prompted 20th Century Fox to delay the release of the film,
and it was then released theatrically in the United States on April 4, 2003.
The film received generally positive reviews from
critics and grossed $97 million worldwide.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.